BUS DAY
PASS
Day two of the class trip...
DAY 2 GROUP ACTIVITIES
TRIP GUIDE
Group activities!
Weren't the fall leaves
and the gardens pretty?
The fall colors were nice...
but the timing didn't work out, did it?
What? T-Timing for what?
Oh, you're pretending you don't know?
We're going the same places as him, right?
"HIM"
Oh, no, that's...
It was just a "maybe we might
see each other."
Being able to take beautiful photos
is enough to make me than happy.
Truthfully, I was just a little hopeful.
You know, instead of going "it would be
nice if we saw each other,"
you could just set a time
and place to meet.
What?
Be alone with him somewhere
other than school?
I could never.
Oh, but... Hon-chan, leaving you
alone so suddenly would be...
Huh? That's your reason? Really?
I'm sorry. That was an underhanded excuse.
All right. You're forgiven.
I hate people who are evasive about
their true feelings, you know?
FWIP
I'm so sorry.
Hey, girls! What are
you two talking about?
Nothing!
SMOOTH
Huh? She lied.
IT HELPS
ME OUT,
THOUGH...
YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
LOVE
FORTUNE
TELLING
STONE
The stones say if your love is real!
My, how lovely.
If you close your eyes and manage
to walk from one stone to the other,
your love will be fulfilled!
What?
Still, it'd be too cringe to do, right?
Me, me! I'll do it!
Wow.
You can do it, Yamada Man!
Go! Go!
Yamada Man!
Yamada's doing it.
Right!
Left!
Reft!
Which way?!
Nice fight!
I'm happy your love will work out.
Morimo!
What are you doing?
Don't get in the way!
No, no.
I'm way bigger than the stone, so the
effectiveness should be greater.
What logic is that?
Hey! I see a bunch of
our uniforms over there.
Is that group 7?
Try talking to him.
What?
No, he's with his friends.
I might be interrupting.
Well, if you're all right with that,
then I guess it's fine, but...
Okay! Look over here!
PESTER
CHATTER
YAY
Stop that, Tani. Smile!
Why make a face
like that for the camera?
Come on! Look this way! Smile! Smile!
Are we little kids?
Suzuki, your face is tense.
Suzuki! Your face is weird!
My face is weird?!
Hurry up and take it.
Your feelings showed!
Oh! Looking good!
Going on your class trip with
a girlfriend must be nice, right?
Sure.
Even if I had one, I'd never
want to be that open about it.
LOVE
I just bought an charm,
so I have high hopes for future me!
Oh! Hey, that's no fair!
And after you got in my way!
I wonder if there's a charm that—
Yamada-kun.
Oh, um, I'm sorry for interrupting
so suddenly. I saw you, so...
GIGGLE
I... thought I'd try
speaking to you. That's all.
Voom!
SUCKING THE
CHARM POWER OUT
Huh? What's all this?
Oh! It's Nissan!
Let's get a photo together!
It's a nice view, isn't it?
What brought that on?
YAMADA, NISHI, HONDA (3)
Oh.
Yamada-kun sent the
pictures from earlier.
Wow. So many photos of
a bizarre group of people.
You're right.
If not for the class trip energy,
we probably wouldn't have taken these.
Honestly, you had the chance.
You should've posed together.
What?
Could we take one with just us two?
With all those people
around, I just couldn't!
Just going up and talking to him used up
all my emotional strength for today.
You did work hard for that.
INCREDIBLE,
NISSHI!
And actually...
GOOD!
PICS FROM EARLIER
Yamada's got problems
without including me.
He should've texted Nisshi privately.
YAMADA, NISHI, HONDA (3)
Moron. Incompetent.
Wasn't this a chance to contact her?
Oh, he texted again.
I wonder if it's a photo.
What kind of photo is it?
YAMADA
UNREAD MESSAGES BELOW
CAN YOU LEAVE
YOUR ROOM RIGHT NOW?
What? He...
He's asking me directly. Wait.
When is "right now"? What do I do?
Go, Nisshi.
What? But, Hon-chan,
I'd be leaving you alone.
There's a livestream I want to watch,
so I won't be bothered.
Oh, but...
Hey, wait up!
I'M IN THE LOBBY
IN A PLACE WITH LOTS OF CHAIRS.
People are wandering around the
hotel a lot more than I thought.
Hey, Yamada!
There's Yamada-kun.
Hiya.
Oh, some girls
I don't know have arrived.
Hey!
Did you go where you wanted?
Yeah, we went everywhere.
Wait. Does this mean that it's possible
I wasn't the only one he called out here?
Later.
Oh, they left.
See you.
Yoohoo!
But now here's someone else.
I've only seen
that greeting done overseas.
Actually, I feel like
Yamada-kun is with girls a lot.
What's this?
For some reason, I've naturally thought of
all of Yamada-kun's actions toward me
REGISTER AS FRIENDS
REGENERATE
as signs of some kind of affection,
and it turned my thinking into a mess.
HE NOTICED...
But what if this is all an
embarrassing misunderstanding?
Like, for me this is something that never
happens, but for Yamada-kun it's normal?
What do I do? I have so little experience
that I never even thought to question it!
Hey.
You should say hi.
Oh, um...
It's just... you were
with other people, so...
Oh. You don't want
other people to see you?
It's, um...
This is bad.
My self-conscious side is showing.
Yeah, you have a point.
Right now, I hate the idea, too.
Right now?
All right.
Let's go and talk quietly
by ourselves.
All the awful imaginings
that were jumbled up in my head
were blown away in an instant.
Yamada-kun's words and actions
are always so straightforward.
Nishi-san, was this cat around
when you went by?
What? No.
It's so cute!
Oh! This is Taira,
the guy I was telling you about...
Oh, I think I've seen him before.
And this is Azuma...
A pretty older sister.
And this bald giant is Morimo.
Morimo?
*MORIMOTO
TAIRA
OUR TURN FOR THE BATH IS COMING UP
Oh.
I've gotta get back.
Y-Yes, me too.
So, um...
Want to go hang out somewhere?
After the class trip.
Like, maybe somewhere we
won't run into anyone from school.
Anywhere is good.
Just the two of us.
Yes.
What do I do?
WHY ME...?
When I think about Yamada-kun's feelings,
there's so much I don't understand.
HOW MUCH
SHOULD I ACCEPT
AS THE TRUTH?
REALLY...?
I hate people who are evasive about
their true feelings, you know?
These feelings of mine...
I can't explain them away anymore.
I love him.
WHEW...
MEANWHILE
Nothing beats my bias.
Back in middle school,
I couldn't say I didn't want to go,
so I reluctantly went,
thinking "I want to hurry up and
go home" as I endured my class trip.
But now...
to be honest...
I'm having fun. A lot of fun.
Class trip, day three!
DAY 3 CLASS ACTIVITIES
TRIP GUIDE
Class activities!
Teacher! Is it okay for me
to get some ice cream?
How casual are you?
Huh? Sure.
It's fine?
I mean, we got around to everything fast.
Right?
Before I knew it, we had
left the other classes behind!
As long as you make it back
before the bus leaves,
you can wander around wherever.
Yeah!
Yay!
Ya—
What?
Oh, nothing.
Stop looking at me like that.
After breaking free of my hometown,
I may accidentally verge
on getting overly excited,
but the moment I see myself
like that, my limiter kicks in.
Especially when I'm with Azuma.
AZUMA KNOWS
THE OLD ME.
BACK THEN, I WAS
LOW-LEVEL, THOUGH.
I DON'T WANT HER
THINKING I'M LIVING IT UP
IN THIS NEW ENVIRONMENT.
All these concerns
mix together into...
An incomplete sense of
self-consciousness and inferiority.
Huh? Where'd that come from?
Oh! Hey, I want to buy some deer senbei!
There's ten in a packet. Shall we share?
Oh, my!
What?
Nothing.
Taira, wanna go halfsies with me?
Okay.
STARE...
Wow! They're already standing by!
They're used to getting fed.
They're really rushing over!
Wait! This is pretty scary!
Whoa! Drool! Calm down!
Stay! Stay! Time out! Stay!
Stay! Wait! Stay!
Yamada sure is talking
to those deer a lot.
Listen to this!
Those deer ate everything they could
eat in a flash and then they all left!
Doesn't look like that's happening there.
I don't have any more!
Taira's so popular with the deer.
Hey! Stop laughing and help me!
Huh?
BUS TOUR STYLE
And now, if I could have your attention
for the return trip!
If you think we're gonna
keep this party going,
throw your hands in the air!
Yay!
Don't give a mid-concert talk.
In the front row! Tani-kun,
how's your car sickness?
TANI
Stop sliding personal info into your talk.
Taira.
Huh?
Over here.
TANI
MOVED
YAMADA
HELPING WITH
THE TALK
And now, I'd like to do a quiz!
SUZUKI
GIVING THE TALK
Here's question 1!
What two animals are hidden
in the Japanese name for April first?
I bought lots of snacks,
so let's eat some.
MIXY MIXY
YON YON
IN NATURE
JIGGLY TAMAPON
KOALA'S MARCH
That's way too many.
Those remind me of an elementary school
field trip. So nostalgic.
Anyone know the answer?
Then it goes to you, Yamada!
Nabe recommended them.
No clue!
Taira? Do you have
a problem with Nabe-chan's choices?
Don't say it so enthusiastically!
The answer is, you take
the "itachi" from "shigatsu tsuitachi,"
I wasn't complaining. Now sit properly.
Oh! Taira, this is one
where there's a lucky piece.
and since that date is also referred to
as "watanuki," the answer is two tanuki!
RUSSIAN ROULETTE GUM
I'll give you one.
Tell me if you win, okay?
Wow.
You didn't understand it at all, did you?
Wow, that's sour.
Your reaction is way too small.
And now for question 3!
Isn't this a normal reaction?
Stop having weird expectations.
What kind of bird do you get
when you've got nine all together?
Over here!
Oh! Zuma-chan! Having an active
participant is so helpful!
A nine-ah bird!
Incorrect! Too bad!
And she got it wrong?
What? But I was so sure it was right.
That was a tough one.
The correct answer is... pigeon!
PIGEON
Huh? Why a pigeon?
Pigeon is written with the
kanji for "nine" and "bird."
Huh? Wait. Are you weirded out
because I was wrong?
Yamada, can you write
the kanji for pigeon?
Huh? No.
It's just... Was Azuma always like this?
Pretty much no.
Are you gonna be okay?
Tani, are you okay?
Dinner tonight is all-you-can-eat!
Can you handle it?
Meat! Meat! Meat!
Don't make him imagine that right now!
I want to feel the wind
for a while. Go on ahead.
Take care!
If you don't know
where to go, just call me!
Thank you.
And of course,
this is the one time I'm out of tea.
It's all right. Thank you.
What? You're having
a cola before a buffet?
There's no need to be that shocked.
No, it's just... I've heard that
cola works for car sickness.
(KNOWLEDGE FROM
THE INTERNET)
That's so kind of you!
OH, MY!
Stop doing stuff like that!
Tani-kun, do you usually get car sick?
No, not usually. Just for some reason...
But I'm all right now.
That's a relief. Maybe you weren't
feeling well to begin with?
We still have tomorrow, too.
I'm all right.
In that case, it gets chilly at night,
so I'll head back to where everyone—
Stay with me just a little longer?
Okay.
What was that?!
I regret ever worrying about him!
That was insane! They're totally living
the springtime of youth! I was shocked!
I saw something great.
That was fun!
It was not good and it was not fun!
Oh, I don't care anymore.
I'll drink this myself.
Argh! Seriously?!
Wait! I can't! My stomach hurts!
Don't laugh at other people's misfortune!
But this is something you laugh at.
Somehow, Azuma, you're more...
classmate-like than I thought.
Huh? Of course I am.
What?
We always talk casually with each other.
And we were in the same class
together last year, right?
What?
Yeah, I mean... That's true, but...
"You've changed somehow"
is what I wanted to, uh...
But what good does saying that do?
That's creepy!
MEANWHILE 2
BA-DUMP BA-DUMP
What?
What was that just now?
BA-DUMP
BA-DUMP BA-DUMP
It's not fair!
BA-DUMP
It was adorable!
FEVERISH
BA-DUMP BA-DUMP
RECOVERED
A WHILE AGO
BA-DUMP
BA-DUMP BA-DUMP
Class trip, the final day!
TRIP GUIDE
Free time!
FINAL DAY FREE TIME
Where should we go first?
We don't have much time, though.
Aren't you going somewhere else?
That was blunt.
Well, enjoy your date.
If we run into you,
we'll pretend we didn't.
It's fine. You don't have to go that far.
Couples tend to argue on
amusement park dates, so be careful.
There you go,
saying stuff like that again.
When a guy has a bad attitude
waiting in lines or driving,
you should assume
that's their true nature.
That's not from experience, is it?
Where do you want to start?
Oh! There's a spot
I want to stop by first!
This is it! A popcorn case!
I wanted to wear this
and walk around!
Isn't it adorable?
Adora...
It seems like your thing.
I want to look at the hats
and headbands and stuff, too!
This is so exciting!
Huh?
Tani-kun, I wasn't expecting that choice.
This...
seems like you'd wear it.
I'd wear it?
You mean it'd look nice on me?
Yeah.
Oh, my!
In that case, which of these
would look good on Tani-kun?
What?
I'm okay without one.
Huh?
O-Oh, really?
That was close! I was getting
all excited on my own again.
If I don't get a grip,
he'll end up next to an avatar
loaded up with paid gacha pulls.
But, I was sort of hoping to do casually
matching headbands or something.
I guess he's not that type.
Oh.
Do you want to buy matching ones?
Sort of... like we did before.
Yeah!
Merch like this is okay,
but headbands are a no-go?
It's just... I can't imagine myself
wearing something like that.
They look good on you,
but I'd look weird, wouldn't I?
What? You wouldn't look weird!
Actually, in places like this,
you should be weird.
You'll regret not going nuts.
Right.
Let's break out of that
shell of yours, Yuusuke-san!
Um...
You don't like the idea!
It's fine! No need to force yourself!
Do you want some? Go ahead.
Thanks.
For some reason, it's starting
to look cuter and cuter to me.
So it wasn't cute to you before?
This is so much fun!
Nabe and the others told me not to argue
because wait times are so long,
but not having fun is harder, right?
NEEDLESS
WORRY
OF THE
YEAR
Yeah, that's true.
But, time-wise, we might not
be able to do anything else.
Really? Already?
I just got a text from Azu.
It looks like everyone else
is together.
I guess we should go and join them!
We have to get ready to
go home already? That's so sad!
Miyu...
...chan.
A BELATED
"-CHAN"...
What's wrong?
Um...
Let's... take the long way there.
Y-Yuusuke-kun... hold on.
Today, you're...
Actually, yesterday, too...
No, actually, before that, too...
Are you trying to kill me?
What?
I don't know why. I...
Maybe I've gone a little weird.
What kind of laugh was that?
Boys, that's crazy!
Why are you all wearing those?
How'd it start?
For the looks.
The crew members asked
about it, right?
LARGE GROUP
I didn't realize that people
greeted each other that much.
FRIENDLY
STARE...
Taira-kun...
What? Why are you only
giving me that reaction?
YOU'RE WEARING ONE...
Hey! Let's all take
a group picture together!
Yay!
Are you thinking you should've
just gone all the way insane?
No.
Okay! I'm taking it now.
Just a little.
In that case...
Say cheese!
We'll have to come back, right?
Yeah.